A Guide to the Rebecca C. Lancefield papers, Rockefeller University Faculty FA173
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Correspondence
  - Kaminsky, Daniel, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Kantor, Fred, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Kaplan, Melvin H, 1959 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Kempf, J.E., 1963-1964 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Klinge, Karl, 1961 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Köhler, W., 1959-1964 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Koenig, M. Glenn, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Krasner, Robert I., 1959-1960 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Krause, Richard M., 1963-1965 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Kusama, Hideo, 1959-1963 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Kuzmanovic, Branislav O., 1961 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Kaplan, Edward L., 1975 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Kaplan, Eugene, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Karakawa, Judy (Kane), 1969 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Karakawa, Walter W., 1967-1968 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Kasper, Dennis L., 1976 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Khan, M. Wajeed, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Kjems, Ebbe, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Koch, Edward I., 1978 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Köhler, W., 1966-1980 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Koshuharov, Bozhidar, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Krampitz, L.O., 1975 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Krause, Richard M., 1966 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Kunz, Lawrence J., 1980 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Kurl, D., 1980 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Kusama, Hideo, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Kuttner, Ann [re], 1970 1972 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Lackman, David B., 1953 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Lamb, Marion E., 1952 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Lambert, Edward C., 1965 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Lancefield, Rebecca C., 1959 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - The Lancet, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Landabure, Pedro B., 1948 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Lane, A.L., 1960-1976 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Langley, L.L., 1970 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Lawy, H., 1952 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Lederberg, Joshua, 1972 1979 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Lee, Wie-Shing, 1977 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Leonard, Christiana M., 1972 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Lewandowski, Thaddeus, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Lewin, Edward B., 1975-1976 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Liao, Sung J., 1948 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Liao, Yen Shyong, 1980 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Liu, Pinghui, 1954-1957 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Lubitz, Joseph M. (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Lyall, Harold W., 1947 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - McClung, L.S., 1957 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - McDonald, Alice, 1953 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - MacLeod, Colin M., 1955 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Mackenzie, G.M., 1949 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Marcus, Stanley, 1947-1950 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Marsh, Homer F., 1947 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Massell, Benedict F., 1947-1950 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Maxted, W.R., 1952-1956 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Meisel, H., 1949 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Mergenhagen, Stephan E., 1957 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Miller, C. Phillip, 1947 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Miller, Joseph M., 1953 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Moore, Ruth E., 1948 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Moreira-Jacob, M., 1958 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Morgan, F.G., 1952 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Morgan, Herbert R., 1951-1956 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Morris, Alton J., 1957 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Moskowitz, Merwin, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Mumma, C.S., 1949 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Murray, F.J., 1949 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - McEwen, Currier, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - McKeen, John E., 1960 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - MacLeod, Colin M., 1958 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Mandy, William J., 1967 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Markowitz, Milton, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Massell, Benedict F., 1961-1965 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Maxted, W.R., 1966 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Mayerhofer, Hans J., 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Medrek, Theodore F., 1965 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Merger, Carl E., 1958-1959 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Michael, J. Gabriel, 1962 1965 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Milgrom, Felix, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Miller, C. Phillip, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Miller, Joseph M., 1962 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Moody, Max D., 1964-1965 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Morton, William, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Moulder, James W., 1964 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Mudd, Stuart, 1966-1967 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Markowitz, Milton, 1968-1970 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Massell, Benedict F., 1968 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Matsen, John M., 1969 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Maxted, W.R., 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Medrek, Theodore F., 1968-1970 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Michel, M.F., 1970 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Modern Medicine, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Moody, Max D., 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Morse, Stephen I., 1969 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Mortimer, Edward A. Jr., 1969 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Mudd, Stuart, 1968-1970 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - McCracken, George H., 1978 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - McKee, Albert P., 1975 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Malke, Horst, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Marsik, Frederic J., 1977-1978 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Martinez, Octavio, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Mathews, James H., 1972 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Maxted, W.R., 1974-1979 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Medrek, Theodore F., 1971 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Metzger, Henry, 1971-1980 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Michel, Mark F., 1972 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Milligan, Tom, 1976 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Moody, Max D., 1971-1978 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Morozumi, Pius A., 1978 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Nantz, Frank A., 1949 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Nardelli, L., 1956 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Negreiros, E. Brum, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Neter, Erwin, 1950 1955 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Neuman, G., 1950 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - New York Academy of Medicine, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Newcomb, Richard W., 1972 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Nicastro, August J., 1971 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Nishimura, Toshio, 1965 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Norcross, Neil L., 1976 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Oakley, L.C., 1972 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Olechowski, Carolyn, 1967 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - de Oliveira, J. Cândido, 1950 1957 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Olmstead, E.V., 1956 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Omori, Gendo, 1958 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Oppenheimer Memorial Committee, J. Robert, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Ortiz de Landàzuri, Eduardo, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Osier, Abraham G., 1949 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Osterman, Björn, 1974 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Ottens, H., 1964 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Ouchterlony, Ö, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - O'Hern, Elizabeth M., 1975-1977 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Parker, R.F., 1956 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Parr, Leland W., 1948 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Parrish, A.E., 1957 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Pattison, I.H., 1948-1954 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Peoples, Don M., 1950 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Perez, J. Enrique, 1954 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Peso, Osvaldo A., 1947-1951 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Peterson, R.F., 1952 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Pettenella, Giuseppe, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Phillips, John H., 1953-1957 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Pierangeli, Enrique, 1948-1949 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Pierce, William A., 1952-1953 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Pillemer, Louis, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Pitner, Georgia, 1952 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Price, Winston H., 1955-1957 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Pusat, Melahat, 1951 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Parker, Thomas, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Parrish, A.E., 1958 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Pathological Society of Great Britain and Ireland, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Payne, Anthony M.-M., 1965 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Perch, B., 1963 1970 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Pettenella, Giuseppe, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Pike, Robert M., 1962 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Potter, Elizabeth V., 1961 1967-1970 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Price, Winston H., 1958 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Prinz, Alexander, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Page, Irvine H., 1971 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Pavlatos, M., 1978 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Pavlova, Maria, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Pazur, John H., 1975 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Pharmacia Diagnostics, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Pohlod, Donald J., 1980 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Polin, Richard A., 1978 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Pollock, J.J., 1977 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Pope, Richard M., 1976 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Potter, Elizabeth V., 1971-1972 1980 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Potts, Arlene, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Prior, Bradley W., 1971 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Rafyi, A., 1953 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Rammelkamp, C.H., 1954 1957 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Rantz, Lovell A., 1948-1949 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Raška, Karel, 1946-1947 1950 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Raven, Clara, 1948-1949 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Reid, J. Douglas, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Rhoads, Cornelius P., 1957 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Riddle, Jackson W., 1950 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Rinehart, R.E., 1954 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Rivers, Thomas M., 1960 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Robertson, L.F., 1947 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Rogers, K.B., 1957-1959 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Romanzi, Carmine A., 1956 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Rose, John. K., 1960 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Rosenthal, Sanford M., 1957 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Rotta, Jiřě, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Roy, T.E., 1955 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Rusnock, Catherine, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Rutstein, David D., 1956 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Ruys, A. Charlotte, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Rabinowitz, S. Bergner, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Rammelkamp, Charles H., 1966 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Rantz, Lovell A., 1961-1962 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Raska, Karel, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Reiss, Albert M., 1967 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Roberts, C. Evans, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Rodriguez, Louis, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Rogers, K.B., 1961 1963 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Rolicka, Maria, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Rose, John, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Rosenberg, S., 1961 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Rosenblum, Herman, 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Rotta, Jiri, 1964-1968 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Ragnhildstveit, Eivind, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Rammelkamp, Charles H., 1976 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Robbins, John B., 1974-1974 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Rodriguez, G.E., 1978 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Romanelli, José Amilcar, 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Rose, J.K., 1969 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Rothbard, Sidney, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Rotta, Jiří, 1969-1971 1974 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Ruch, Frank E., 1974 1980-1981 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Russell, Catherine M., 1973 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Russell, Harold, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Saltzman, Mollie, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Saslaw, Milton S., 1953 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Schelhart, Dorothy, 1952-1953 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Schmidt, Willard C., 1952 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Schleimer, Mildred, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Schuhardt, V.T., 1949-1950 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Schultz, Mark P., 1950 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Schwarz, Levis H., 1953 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Seal, John R., 1951-1952 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Servi, Marco, 1953 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Sherman, J.M., 1949-1952 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Sherwood, Noble P., 1950-1954 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Shichikawa, Kanji, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Slade, Hutton D., 1951 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Smith, Mary H., 1950 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Smolens, Joseph, 1950 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Smythe, Richard (Mrs), 1951 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Solowey, Mathilde, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Stableforth, A.W., 1950 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Stamp, Lord, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Stavitsky, Abram B., 1950 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Stetson, Chandler A., 1952 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Stillerman, Maxwell, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Stock, A.H., 1950-1953 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Stock, J.J., 1951 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Swift, Homer F., 1951 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Swineford, Oscar, 1951 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Sallman, Bennett, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Sanders, Murray, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Saphra, Ivan, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Saslaw, Milton S., 1955 1957 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Saunders, Maridel, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Scherago, M., 1957 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Scherp, Henry W., 1956 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Schlesinger, R. Walter, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Schultz, Selma, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Seeley, H.W., 1955 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Sherwood, Noble P., 1955 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Shichikawa, K., 1955 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Shimizu, K., 1956-1957 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Slade, Hutton D., 1955-1956 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Slanetz, L.W., 1955 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Smith, Ian Maclean, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Smith, Mary H., 1955 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Smolin, H.J., 1956 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Stanfield, Alice B., 1955 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Stock, Aaron H., 1955 1957 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Saslaw, Milton S., 1958-1961 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Schieffelin and Co., 1958 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Schmidt, Willard C., 1958-1960 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Schuhardt, V.T., 1959 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Schwab, John H., 1958 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Sharp, John T., 1959-1961 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Shattock, P.M. Frances, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Sheinfield, Henry, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Sherwood, Noble P., 1958 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Shetlar, M.R., 1960 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Shiomi, Toshiro, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Slade, Hutton D., 1958-1961 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Solé-Vernin, Carlos, 1961 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Stock, Aaron H., 1958-1961 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Svartz, Nanna, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Schmidt, Willard C., 1962 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Seeley, H.W. Jr., 1965 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Shands, A.R. Jr., 1964 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Addendum: Smith, Mary Ruth, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Sharp, John T., 1962 1965 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Sharpe, Dr., 1964 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Shattock, P.M. Frances, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Silva, Ramiro Martinez, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Smith, Thomas B., 1964-1965 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Snyder, Sylvia, 1964 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Sole-Vernin, Carlos, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Šràmek, J., 1965 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Stock, Aaron H., 1962-1965 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Svartz, Wanna, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Seal, Marjorie, 1966 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Schiebler, G.L., 1969 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Schmidt, Willard C., 1966-1971 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Shioiri-Nakano, Kohei, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Smith, H., 1967 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Smith, Theobald B., 1966 1971 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Šrámek, J., 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Stock, Aaron H., 1966 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Sabin, Florence [re], 1975 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Sasaki, Makoto, 1975 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Sato, Maroto, 1977 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Schalla, William O., 1972 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Schein, Catherine H., 1978 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Schmidt, Willard, 1976 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Schoenknecht, Fritz D., 1974 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Seitz, Frederick, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Sell, Samuel L., 1975 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Sery, Theodore W., 1972 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Skerman, V.B.D., 1973 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Slade, Hutton D., 1975 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Smith, Gerald L., 1975 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Smith, H., 1972 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Spitznagel, John K., 1975 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Starr, Mortimer D., 1973 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Swenson, Robert M., 1977-1978 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Stollerman, Gene H., 1955-1976 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Tiffany, Elberton J., 1947-1948 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Tillett, William S., 1948 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Todd, E.W., 1948 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Tappan, Vivian, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Tarata, Angelo, 1969-1972 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Tepper, Byron, 1958 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Thirumoorthi, M.C., 1977 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Thomson, Annis E., 1953 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Thornsberry, Clyde, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Tiffany, Elberton J., 1949 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Tillett, William S., 1950 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Todd, Edgar W. [re], 1958 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Toharsky, Beatrice, 1953 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - De Toma de Barjacoba, Francisca, 1961 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Turner, G.S., 1949 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Tyler, Albert, 1962 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Typlin, Bonnie L., 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Valkenburg, Hans A., 1972 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Vanderboom, Katherine J., 1947 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Van Loon, Ethel T., 1949-1951 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Veltsos, A.G., 1955 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Venegas Cantu, Maria M., 1969 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Vermillion, Lythene, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Verna, Luis C., 1963-1965 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Verwey, W.F., 1948 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Vestal, Patricia, 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Vicher, Edward E., 1946-1949 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Vivanco, Adolfo, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Voigt, E.F., 1947 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Vosti, Kenneth L., 1969 1971 1978-1979 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Wagner, Vladimìr, 1947-1948 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Wahl, R., 1953 1955 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Walcher, Dwain N., 1949-1950 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Waldo, John F., 1947 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Wallace, G.I., 1947 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Wannamaker, Lewis W., 1949 1953 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Warner, Douglas, 1951 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Warren, Joseph E., 1948 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Watson, Dennis W., 1955 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Weil, A.J., 1948 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Weil, Harry R., 1950 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Weinstein, Louis, 1949-1951 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Weiss, Charles, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Weiss, Freeman A., 1954 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Wenner, Herbert A., 1948-1950 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Whitaker, L.G., 1950 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Wiley, Grove G., 1954 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Wilt, J.C., 1949 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Winkler, C.H. Jr., 1951 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Winter, C.E., 1953 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Wolman, Irving J., 1953 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Wood, Ronald M., 1948 1953 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Wood, W. Barry Jr., 1957 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Wahl, Robert, 1956-1963 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Wallace, G.I., 1957 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Wannamaker, Lewis, 1957-1963 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Wasielewski, E., 1956 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Weiss, D.W., 1959 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - White, R.G., 1959 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Wiken, T., 1953 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Wiley, Grove G., 1956-1960 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Williams, R.E.O., 1956-1959 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Wood, Harrison F., 1960 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Woods, Alan C., 1961 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Woodson, Robert D., 1960 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Wyckoff, Delaphine G.R., 1956 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Wannamaker, Lewis W., 1964-1965 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Western College for Women, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Wieder, Miriam C., 1965 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Wiley, Grove G., 1964-1965 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Williams, R.E.O., 1965 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Wannamaker, Lewis W., 1966-1970 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Weaver, Robert E., 1966 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Western College for Women, 1966-1968 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Wiggins, R.C., 1968 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Wikler, Maurice, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Wiley, Grove G., 1966-1970 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Wilkinson, Hazel W., 1970 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Williams, R.E.O., 1968 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Wilson, Graham S., 1966 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Wood, Harrison F., 1966 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Wood, W. Barry Jr., 1966 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Woolcock, John B., 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Wannamaker, Lewis W., 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Wellesley College Alumnae Association, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Wiley, Grove G., 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Wilkinson, Hazel W., 1972 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Williams, R.E.O., 1972 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Wyatt, H.V., 1972 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Walter, E.L., 1974 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Wannamaker, Lewis, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Wasserman, Elga, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Weisburd, Martin H., 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Wellesley College, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Wennerstrom, David E., 1976 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Wheat, Robert W., 1975 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Wildfeuer, A., 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Wilkinson, Hazel W., 1973-1978 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Wolff, Arlene G. ca, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Wilson, Amine T., 1947-1964 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - World Health Organization, 1957-1960 1973 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Yost, Edna, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Young, Dora E., 1960 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Young, Genevieve, 1955 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Yow, Martha, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Yurick, Elias I., 1956 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Zeiger, Allen R., 1974 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Zimmerman, Robert A., 1970-1973 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Zygmunt, Walter A., 1950 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - American Society for Microbiology, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Avery, Minnie, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Avery, O.T. [re], 1964 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Baker, Carol J., 1974-1978 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Barkulis, S.S., 1966 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - British Society for Immunology, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Bruno, Pauline, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Buescher, Georganne K., 1977 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Burnham, Robert, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Bynoe, E.T., 1942-1943 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Campbell, Charlotte C., 1975 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Campo, Tony, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Cockrell, Janice L., 1980 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Cole, Rufus, 1955 1957 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Colebrook, Vera, 1967-1968 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Colman, G., 1960 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Crowley, Nuala, 1950 1957 1970 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Curnen, Ed, 1974 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Duncan, James L., 1980 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Ederer, Grace Mary, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Elliott, Stuart D., 1951 1979 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Elliott, Stuart (?) [Public Health Service Laboratory, Colindale], circa 1959 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Fauve, Robert M., undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Ferrieri, Patricia, 1980 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Fleming, Diane O., 1978 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Francis, A.E., 1942 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Frost, Heiner, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Fry, R.M., 1966 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Furth, Jacob, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Gelfand, Michael C., 1978 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Gezon, Horace M., 1966 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Glaser, Robert J., 1956 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Harvey Lecture [re], 1941 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Haug, Rangdi Holth, 1975-1978 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Hayashi, Takayoshi, 1968 1976-1977 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Heever, LW vd, 1978 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Heyer, Berno, 1975 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Hirst, R.G., 1974 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Hitchcock, C.H., 1961 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Hon, Mrs. Conrad (Jessie), 1973 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Hook, E.W., 1959 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Hwang, Joseph C., 1976 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Jelínková, Jarmila, 1975 1977 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Johnson, Rudolph H., 1978 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Journal of Experimental Medicine [Rebecca C. Lancefield mss], 1958 1959 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Kaplan, Edward L., 1980 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Katz, Samuel L., 1976 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Kennedy, Robert F., 1966 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Krause, Richard M., 1964 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Kunitz, Dr., 1973 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Kuttner, Ann, 1957 1963-1966 undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Lancefield, Rebecca C., 1954 1957-1959 1965 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Lane, A.L., 1956 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Laughton, Nancy, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - McCormack, James E., 1968 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - McCracken, George H., 1978 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - MacLeod, Colin M., 1942 [re] 1972 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Maekawa, Shizue, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Mandlebaum, Ruth, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Maxted, W.R., 1952 1971 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Milgrom, Felix, 1960 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Moody, Max, 1965-1966 1970 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - National Academy of Sciences, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Noguchi, H. TV program, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Nollstadt, Karl, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - O'Hern, Elizabeth, 1975-1976 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Opie, Eugene, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Owen, Cora Rust, 1959-1967 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - O'Hern, Elizabeth Draft of ms with Rebecca C. Lancefield changes (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Potter, Elizabeth, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Rafyi, A., 1953 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Raska, K., 1964 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Repine, John E., 1977 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Rockefeller, David, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Rogers, K.B., 1960 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Rotta, J., 1973 1975 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Ruys, A. Charlotte, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Sabin, Florence, 1934 1951 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Sato, Maroto, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Schoenknecht, Fritz D., 1974 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Shands, A.R. Jr., 1967 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Shulman, Stanford T., 1980 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Smith, Homer P., 1980 (Box 9, Folder 13)